{"submissions":[{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"3","solvers":["lukas"],"time":"15:58","correct":true},{"color":"admin","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":[],"time":"22:13","correct":true,"id":65496113619609.41},{"color":"admin","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":[],"time":"22:15","correct":true,"id":44231495383850.27},{"color":"admin","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":[],"time":"22:17","correct":true,"id":59475360495704.39},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"0","solvers":[],"time":"21:3","correct":false,"id":33313712770214.29},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"0","solvers":["ota dvorak","julia cerna"],"time":"22:17","correct":false,"id":48697576658924.18},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"0","solvers":["ota dvorak","julia cerna"],"time":"22:18","correct":false,"id":34760423884757.684},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["ota dvorak","julia cerna"],"time":"22:18","correct":true,"id":80584865304900.5},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["ota dvorak","julia cerna"],"time":"22:19","correct":true,"id":58456866549052.47},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["ota dvorak","julia cerna"],"time":"22:19","correct":true,"id":37081471635164.93},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["ota dvorak"],"time":"22:25","correct":true,"id":37723483342661.516},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["lukas"],"time":"22:36","correct":true,"id":73315908310994.55},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["lukas"],"time":"22:37","correct":true,"id":51598078482656.34},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["lukas"],"time":"22:38","correct":true,"id":94432758055391.9},{"color":"red","question":"1","answer":"1.54","solvers":["lukas"],"time":"22:45","correct":true,"id":36652712333381.3}]}